kodak.com 2016-12-24

# PrivacyPolicy-US-2016 | Kodak

Updated October 2016

#### Our Commitment to Privacy

At Eastman Kodak Company _(343 State Street, Rochester, NY 14650_ , _USA_ , "Kodak"), we are committed to protecting your privacy. Our pledge is to safeguard any personal information that you provide us and to make every reasonable effort to use this information only as you choose. Kodak is committed to using your personal information appropriately and making Kodak's internet presence a safe and secure place for you to transact online. 

#### Scope of This Notice

This Online Privacy Notice applies to Kodak websites, applications, blogs and other digital offerings. The goal of this Online Privacy Notice is to inform you of the choices you have about the way the information collected is used. It also applies to consumer digital registration cards. For information about other offline data collections, use the contact information noted below.

PLEASE NOTE:

  * If you provide your personal information on kodak.com or one of our mobile apps and you indicate your residence is outside the U.S., or if you choose your location using the kodak.com change country link, you may be offered a privacy notice that is specific to your country of residence. 
  * On our co-branded sites (such as those sites where Kodak has presented content together with one of our retail partners), a privacy notice unique to that site may be presented.
  * Private sites (such as those only available to dealers and distributors) and sites created for our employees (or prospective employees) may also have privacy notices unique to those sites.
  * Sites maintained by Kodak subsidiaries, affiliates, and brand licensed partners, although linked to kodak.com, have their own online privacy notices.

#### Your Personal Information

Kodak's goal in collecting personal information about you is, first, to give you a meaningful, enjoyable and personalized website experience and, second, to facilitate the development of new products and services relevant to customers like you. Personal information also allows us to provide better service to you by tailoring our communications to match your interests – deliver more of what you want and less of what you don't want.

Here are the types of information we gather:

  * **Information You Explicitly Provide.** In order to establish your account, register products, or to participate in various online programs offered through Kodak, you will be asked to provide certain personally identifiable information to us such as your name, mailing address, e-mail address, and phone number. You can choose not to provide this information but then you might not be able to participate in some of our services or offerings.
  * **Information We Automatically Collect.** We use common internet technologies such as cookies and beacons to ensure the integrity of our site and to customize portions of the site for you.
    * **IP Address:**  We analyze IP addresses in the aggregate for system administration purposes and to gather broad demographic information. We do not link IP addresses to your computer's User ID. ****
    * **Cookies:  **This website makes use of first-party and third-party cookies (for profiling purposes) to give you the best, most optimized user experience, to improve our website and to show you advertising according to your preferences. You can change your cookie settings at any time, but parts of this website will not function correctly without them. By continuing to browse this website without changing your settings, we will consider that you consent to the use of cookies and other trackers as set out in our Cookie Notice. For more information about cookies and how to disable them, please see our Cookie Notice. 

#### Customer Export Order Screening 

Kodak employs technology and uses public watch list data obtained from [http://mkdataservices.com](http://mkdataservices.com/) to screen all export orders in compliance with US Federal and International rules and regulations regarding export controls for denied and restricted parties.

#### Location Services

When you use our website or download our mobile apps, you may choose to allow us to obtain your precise location. We use this information to customize our response to your requests. For example, if you are searching for a theater providing film projection services, we will display the ones in your area; we may share your location with third party mapping services (e.g., Apple Maps, Google Maps) to accomplish this. We may also offer automatic (or "push") notifications. We will provide push notifications only to those customers who opt-in to receive such notifications from us. You do not have to provide location information to us or enable push notifications to use any of our mobile apps. If you have questions about location and notification privacy, please contact your mobile service provider or the manufacturer of your device to learn how to adjust your settings.

#### Using Your Information

Kodak only uses the personal information you explicitly provide to conduct business with you. This includes:

  * registering you in programs
  * registering products
  * creating and maintaining accounts
  * processing, fulfilling, and following up on orders, as applicable
  * answering your e-mail
  * providing news about Kodak products, offers, software upgrades, services, tips and projects
  * sending surveys
  * analyzing aggregate data to increase our understanding of our customers and our ability to meet their needs

We also use this personal information to 

  * provide you with information related to your account, the products or services you purchased from us 
  * understand your needs and interests 
  * improve our service
  * personalize communications

#### Does Kodak Share Your Information?

Your personally identifiable information will not be rented or sold to any third party. Kodak may share your personal information as follows:  ****

  * **Companies who work on our behalf** : We contract with other companies to perform business support functions on our behalf, which may involve limited access to your personal information. We require these companies to use the information only to provide the contracted services; they are prohibited from transferring the information to another party except as needed to provide those services. Some examples of these business support functions include order fulfillment, customer survey execution, marketing emails, and information systems management. We also may make aggregate information available to select service providers. Some of these partners may store your data outside of the European Union. In all cases, Kodak’s contracts with these vendors require compliance with applicable laws and best practices and assesses their data protection capabilities. 
  * **Kodak's subsidiaries and joint ventures:**  A subsidiary or a joint venture is an organization in which Kodak owns at least a 50% interest. Kodak may share your personal information with Kodak’s subsidiaries and joint ventures to allow you to receive marketing and product information. If Kodak shares your information with a subsidiary or joint venture partner, Kodak will require that they not transfer your information to another party for marketing purposes or use your information contrary to your expressed choices. If you have indicated that you do not want to receive any marketing information from Kodak, we will not share your information with our subsidiary or joint venture partner for their marketing purposes. Some of these subsidiaries and joint ventures may store your data outside of the European Union. Kodak’s Privacy Policy requires that all subsidiaries and joint ventures comply with EU legal requirements and data protection best practices. 
  * **Co-branded and Partner Pages:**  Kodak may share information with partner companies who jointly present special offers or promotions on co-branded pages within our site. You will be notified of this sharing when you are asked to furnish personal data on such a page. The partner's use of any information you submit will be governed by the partner's own privacy notice, which you can review before submitting your information
  * **Business Transfers:**  Kodak reserves the right to transfer your personal information in connection with the sale or transfer of all or a portion of our business or assets, to the extent permitted by applicable law. If the business is sold or transferred, Kodak will give you an opportunity to tell us not to transfer your personal information. In some cases, this may mean that the new organization will not be able to continue providing to you the services or products that Kodak provided.
  * **Law Enforcement:**  Kodak may disclose personal information to third parties without your consent for any of the following reasons: to comply with any law, regulation or court order; to cooperate with government investigations; to help prevent fraud or to enforce or protect the rights of Kodak.

#### Your Choices about Receiving E-mail

Kodak may send you e-mail about your orders or your account and in response to your questions. Kodak and its subsidiaries may also send you e-mail with information and/or special offers about products and services that may be of interest to you, provided you agreed to receive such e-mails in accordance with applicable law.

We will give you an opportunity to let us know your preference regarding the receipt of promotional e-mail. This option applies to promotional e-mail only, as we may find it necessary to send you e-mail relating to your account, order, product or pricing changes.

Promotional e-mail that you receive from Kodak will tell you how to decline receiving future promotional e-mail. For additional information about declining e-mail from Kodak, visit [www.kodak.com/go/suppressemail](http://www.kodak.com/go/suppressemail). 

#### Protecting Your Information

Kodak implements a variety of administrative, managerial and technical security measures to help protect your personal information in line with applicable laws and regulations. Kodak has Internal Control Standards which relate specifically to the handling of personal information. These include certain controls to help safeguard the information we collect online. Kodak stores your data in the United States.  Kodak’s Privacy Policy requires that all our data protection complies with EU legal requirements and data protection best practices. 

Kodak employees are trained to understand and comply with these controls, and we communicate our Online Privacy Notice, practices and guidelines to our employees. However, while we strive to protect your personal information, you must also take steps to protect your information. We urge you to take every precaution to protect your personal information while you are on the internet.

#### Communities

Some of our sites may enable you to participate in public services such as discussion boards, chats, and live events. Please use discretion when posting personal data about yourself when using these services. Be aware that when you disclose personal data at these sites, such as your name, member name, e-mail address, etc., the information may be collected and used by others to send unsolicited e-mail. The services are open to the public, and what you post there can be seen by anyone and is not protected. Kodak cannot control the comments that you may receive while you participate in these services. You may find other people's comments to be offensive, harmful or inaccurate.

#### Outside Links

Some Kodak websites contain links to and from other websites, such as social media sites like Facebook and Twitter. Kodak is not responsible for the privacy practices of those websites. Kodak encourages you to ascertain the privacy practices of those websites.

#### Keeping Your Information Accurate

If you are a registered user, you can review and update your profile using your user name and password. You can also contact your Customer Service Representative. 

#### Social Security Number Protection Policy Statement

Kodak may collect Social Security numbers in the ordinary course of its business. Kodak has implemented reasonable technical, physical and administrative safeguards to help protect the Social Security numbers from unlawful use and unauthorized disclosure. All associates and contractors are required to follow these established procedures, both online and offline. Access to Social Security numbers is limited to those employees and contractors who have a need to access the information to perform tasks for Kodak. Social Security numbers are only disclosed to those service providers, auditors, advisors, and/or successors-in-interest who are legally or contractually obligated to protect them or as required or permitted by law.

#### Your Rights

You have the right under applicable law to access, correct, update, erase and block your personal information. In some circumstances, you may have the right to object to processing of your personal information. To exercise your rights please contact [privacy@kodak.com](mailto:privacy@kodak.com). 

#### How to Reach Us

If you have questions or concerns about your privacy when using a Kodak website, please contact us by e-mail at [privacy@kodak.com](mailto:privacy@kodak.com) or by mail at:   
Eastman Kodak Company   
Privacy Office   
13th Floor, Bldg. 7   
343 State Street   
Rochester, NY 14650-0205

Kodak's Privacy Office will work with you to resolve any concerns you have about this Notice.

Kodak commits to resolve complaints about your privacy and our collection or use of your personal information. European Union or Swiss citizens with inquiries or complaints regarding this privacy policy should first contact the Kodak Privacy Office referenced above.

#### Changes to this Online Privacy Notice

Kodak reserves the right to modify this Online Privacy Notice from time to time by posting a prominent announcement on this page or, in the event of a material change, by notifying by e-mail all customers whose personal information we have retained.
